trainpetdog.com 2019-06-20

# Privacy Policy

**Dog Facts **& **Information,  
_Honest Review_ On _Dog Breeds_ ,   
All About Dog Training **& **Care** ****  

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy will be effective from the 26th of June, 2004. 

**Spamming**

We do not spam. If you receive any unsolicited bulk email mentioning this domain, please report it to us immediately. We shall investigate and deal with your complaint promptly. We have a zero tolerance approach towards spam. 

**Personally Identifiable Information**

This web site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information may include your name, your email address and your Dog's name. In case you order any of our products, you will have to furnish information on your location, mailing address, and your phone number. 

**Why are we collecting your personal information?**

The mini course on Dog Training and the Potty Training courses have been developed after a lot of reasearch and practical experimentation. 

The topics that have been covered in the FREE courses have been shortlisted only after conducting customer surveys. 

We collect email addresses so that we can promote a few products to you and recover the costs of developing these free courses, hosting the website, the bandwidth etc. 

**How shall we use, or potentially use, your personal information?**

Your personal information may be used to send you emails or postal mails about special offers that may be relevant to you. 

You will be invited to participate in the Blog and can take part in surveys, contests, product reviews and general discussions. You will be able to interact with several other dog owners across the world. 

You can contact us at any time to know the details of your personally identifiable information that is stored with us, to request changes to it, and to delete it. 

**What options do you have to easily limit the use of your personal information?**

Each of our emails contain a link to unsubscribe from our mailing lists. This link is mostly present at the bottom of the email. 

Whenever, you wish to discontinue, you can simply click on the Unsubscribe link. 

It is a one-step, simple and easy process. And once you unsubscribe, you will not hear from us anymore. 

**Legal Basis for Processing Your Personal Information**

When you sign up for our mini course, we are processing and storing your data on the basis of consent. We will retain this data until such time as you ask us to remove it. When you purchase one of our products, we are processing and storing your data on the basis of our legitimate interest to prevent payment fraud. This data will be retained indefinitely. You have the right to complain to the concerned authorities if you think there is a problem with the way we have handled your data. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. The fact that this privacy policy has changed will be communicated to you by means of a notice that will be put up at the bottom of this page. It is your responsibility to monitor this page on a regular basis for any changes to this privacy policy. 

**Third Parties**

We have contracted with Overture services, Inc. (“Overture”) to monitor certain pages of our Web site for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our site. Where authorized by us, Overture may use cookies, Web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics on our Web site visitors. No personally identifiable data is collected by or transferred to Overture. For more information about how the information collected by Overture is used, please see Overture’s privacy policy at http://www.overture.com/d/USm/about/company/ccprivacyPolicy.jhtml 

**Notification of Changes to Privacy Policy**

The privacy policy was changed on the 8th of May, 2018.
